<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<elements>
	<info>
		<name>Custom Items</name>
		<update version="1.0.0">
			<file name="items-custom.xml" url="none" />
		</update>
	</info>
	<element name="Bag of Hefty Storage Capacity - Baggington" type="Magic Item" source="Dave's Brain" id="ID_CHSCK83_MAGIC_ITEM_BAG_OF_HEFTY_STORAGE_CAPACITY_BAGGINGTON">
		<description>
			<p>This bag has an interior space considerably larger than its outside dimensions, roughly 8 feet in diameter at the mouth and 100 feet deep. No one knows the amout this bag can hold. The bag weighs 15 pounds, regardless of its contents. Retrieving an item from the bag requires an action if it's in the main area of the bag.</p>
			<p class="indent">If the bag is burned, pierced, or torn, it ruptures and is destroyed, and its contents are scattered in a random plane. If the bag is turned inside out, nothing happens, but the bag must be put right before it can be used again. Breathing creatures inside the bag can survive.</p>
			<p class="indent">Placing a this bag inside an extradimensional space created by a <em>handy haversack</em>, <em>portable hole</em>, or similar item does nothing. </p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="category">Wondrous Items</set>
			<set name="cost" currency="gp">0</set>
			<set name="weight" lb="15">15 lb.</set>
			<set name="stash" lb="500" weightless="true">true</set>
			<set name="type">Wondrous Item</set>
			<set name="rarity">Uncommon</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Soul of Frost" type="Magic Item" source="Dave's Brain" id="ID_CHSCK83_MAGIC_ITEM_SOUL_OF_FROST">
		<description>
			<p>This belt is constructed of pale leather and long white threads. It is mildly cool to the touch, and it is very durable. It's said to be made from the body of an ancient frost giant royal/god named Laufey.</p>
			<p>While wearing this belt the following apply:</p>
			<p>Your Strength score changes to 23. The item has no effect on you if your Strength without the belt is equal to or greater than the belt’s score.</p>
			<p>You can exist comfortably in conditions between -50 and 140 degrees Fahrenheit.</p>
			<p>You have advantage on saving throws against cold, and you have resistance against cold damage.</p>
			<p>You have proficiency with and advantage on attack rolls with Great Axes.</p>
			<p>Your Constitution increases by 1.</p>
			<p>At 8th level, you gain the ability to cast Cone of Cold once per long rest. Your constitution affects the Save DC of this spell.</p>
			<p>Anyone who wears this belt will be hated by all Frost Giants and after reaching 7th level, will periodically find themself hunted by icy creatures from other planes</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"></set>
			<set name="category">Wondrous Items</set>
			<set name="cost" currency="gp">0</set>
			<set name="weight" lb="0">0 lb.</set>
			<set name="slot">waist</set>
			<set name="type">Wondrous Item</set>
			<set name="attunement">true</set>
			<set name="rarity">Legendary</set>
		</setters>
		<rules>
			<stat name="strength:score:set" value="23" bonus="base" />
			<stat name="constitution" value="1" />
			<grant type="Proficiency" id="ID_PROFICIENCY_WEAPON_PROFICIENCY_GREATAXE" />
			<grant type="Condition" id="ID_INTERNAL_CONDITION_DAMAGE_RESISTANCE_COLD"/>
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Weapon Tag, +1" type="Magic Item" source="Dave's Brain" id="ID_CHSCK83_MAGIC_ITEM_WEAPON_TAG_1">
	<description>
	<p>You have a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</p>
	</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="category">Wondrous Items</set>
			<set name="cost" currency="gp">0</set>
			<set name="type" addition="any">Weapon</set>
			<set name="rarity">Uncommon</set>
			<set name="enhancement">1</set>
			
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Enhanced Bracers of Defense" type="Magic Item" source="Dave's Brain" id="ID_WOTC_DMG_MAGIC_ITEM_BRACERS_OF_DEFENSE">
        <description>
            <p>While wearing these bracers, you gain a +5 bonus to AC if you are wearing no armor and using no shield.</p>
        </description>
        <setters>
            <set name="keywords">armor</set>
            <set name="category">Wondrous Items</set>
            <set name="cost" currency="gp">0</set>
            <set name="weight" lb="0">0 lb.</set>
            <set name="slot">arms</set>
            <set name="type">Wondrous Item</set>
            <set name="attunement">true</set>
            <set name="rarity">Rare</set>
        </setters>
        <rules>
            <stat name="ac:misc" value="5" equipped="[armor:none],[shield:none]" />
        </rules>
    </element>
</elements>